Guide to the Washington State University Capital Planning Building Files 1957-1998
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Fine Arts Center - Mechanical Systems Renovations. 95% Construction Document Submittal. 3/1988. / Halvorson, Beach and Bower, Inc.; Waldron Pomeroy Smith Foote and Akira ArchitectsRobert Fossatti Associates Sparling and Associates, Inc. (Box 8)
- Fine Arts Plaza - Project Manual. 5/1995. / Architect: ALSC Architects; Structural Consultant: Structural Design NWLandscape Consultant: T.C. Sherry and Associates, P.S.; Electrical Engineer: DEI Electrical Consultants, Inc. (Box 8)
- Fine Arts - Building Program. Life Safety Requirements - Mechanical Systems Renovation. 10/1987. (Box 8)
- Fine Arts - Design Disciplines Building. 6/1967. / Naramore, Bain, Brady and Johanson (Box 8)
- Fine Arts Building - Mechanical Systems Renovations. Schematic Design Phase Submittal. 11/1987. / Halvorson, Beach and Bower, Inc.; Waldron, Pomeroy, Smith, Foote and Akira, ArchitectsRobert Fossatti Associates; Sparling and Associates, Inc. (Box 8)
- Fine Arts Building Plaza - Schematic Design Analysis. 1/1995. / ALSC Architects (Box 8)
- Food and Nutrition Facility - Site Selection Study. 9/1983. / Burke/Lee A Joint Venture (Box 9)
- Food Proc. and Pilot Plant - Proposed Building Plan. 6/1983. (Box 9)
- Food - Human Nutrition Facility - Building Program. 9/1984. (Box 9)
- Food and Human Nutrition Facility - Schematic Design Phase. 5/1986. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 9)
- Food - Human Nutrition Facility - Phase II Schematic Design Presentation. Area Comparison Table and Cost Estimate. 10/1988. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 9)
- Food - Human Nutrition Facility. Phase II - 95% Construction Document Submittal/Program updates. 11/1989. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 9)
- Food - Human Nutrition Facility Phase II - Design Development Presentation. 4/1989. / Northwest Architectural Company; Structural Design Northwest. Inc. and Peden, Petersen and Lee. P.S.Thomas J. Gerard and Associates, Inc.; Wanless-Cook Associates; Milten (Box 9)
- Food - Human Nutrition Facility Phase II - Plan Holders List, Addendum #3 and Bid Tabulation Form. 3/1990. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 9)
- Food - Human Nutrition Facility Phase II - Project manual. Volume I of II Architectural/Structural. 2/1990. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 9)
- Food - Human Nutrition Facility Phase II - Project Manual. Volume II of II Mechanical/Electrical. 2/1990. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 9)
- Food - Human Nutrition Facility - Specifications. 6/1989. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 9)
- Food and Nutrition Facility (New Science Facility) - Proposal for Architectural Services - Support Document. / Hummel Jones Miller Hunsucker, P.A. Arthru Erickson Architects (Box 9)
- Food - Service Building Addition - Building Program. 4/1985. (Box 9)
- Food - Service (Housing and Food Service Facility) - Design Development. 11/1985. / Miller/Hull Partnership (Box 9)
- Food - Service Equipment Specifications. 8/1985. / Walker McGough Foltz Lyeria, P.S. (Box 9)
- Food - Service Building Addition - Specifications. 9/1986. / Miller/Hull (Box 9)
- Food Services Building Addition - Specifications Landscape Work. 4/1988. / Miller/Hull (Box 9)
- Food Services Building Addition - Specifications Landscape Bid. 1989. / Miller/Hull (Box 9)
- Food Service (Housing) Facility - Schematics. 6/1985. / Miller/Hull (Box 9)
- Feed Preparation Mixing and Storage Facility - Site Study. 12/1985. / Burke/Lee A Joint Venture. Architects, Landscape Architects, Planners (Box 10)
- Feed Preparation, Mixing and Storage Facility - Building Program. 7/1985. (Box 10)
- Feed Preparation Mixing and Storage Facility - Design Development. 7/1986. / ARC Architects (Box 10)
- Feed Preparation Mixing and Storage Facility - Schematic Design. / ARC Architects (Box 10)
- Feed Preparation Mixing and Storage Facility - Project Manual. 5/1987. / ARC Architects (Box 10)
- Fieldhouse - Concept Study. 7/1997. / ALSC Architects, P.S.; Riley Engineering - Mechanical and Electrical EngineersStructural Design Northwest - Structural Engineers (Box 10)
- New Administration Building - Program Statement. 12/1964. (Box 10)
- New Administration Building - Schematic Design Brochure. 12/1964. / Worthington. Skilling, Helle and Jackson - Structural Engineers; James B. Notkin. and Associates - Mechanical Engineers; Thomas E. Sparling and Associates - Electrical Engineers; Richard Haag and Associates - Landscape Architects; Robin M. Towne and Associates - Acoustical Consultants (Box 10)
- Greenhouse Replacements Contract 1 - Headhouse and Site Improvements, Puyallup Research and Extension Center. 3/1996. / Stafford Harris, Inc.; Bouillon Christofferson and Schairer. Inc. (Box 10)
- Greenhouse Replacements Contract 2 - Greenhouses, Puyallup Research and Extension Center. 3/1996. / Stafford Harris, Inc.; Bouillon Christofferson and Schairer, inc. (Box 10)
- Greenhouse Replacements Contract 3 - New Campus Electrical Upgrade, Puyallup Research and Extension Center - Specifications. 4/1995. / Stafford Harris. Inc.; Bouillon Christofferson and Schairer, Inc. (Box 10)
- Greenhouse - Headhouse Facilities Building Program, Puyallup Research and Extension Center. 9/1994. (Box 10)
- Greenhouse Replacements Puyallup - Schematic Design CO 11611. 12/1994. / Stafford Harris, Inc.; Sub-Consultants: Bouillon Christofferson and Schairer. Inc.; AKB Consulting Engineers (Box 10)
- Greenhouse Replacements - Design Development/Puyallup WWREC. 2/1995. / Stafford Harris, Inc. (Box 10)
- Greenhouse Replacements - Schematic Design Submittal WWREC. / Stafford Harris, Inc. (Box 10)
- Golf Storage Building - Specifications. 2/1984. / Cambell Engineers, Inc. (Box 10)
- Goldsworthy Hall Renovation - Building Program. 8/1985. (Box 10)
- Gannon/Golds - Mens Residence Halls - Design and Cost Submittal. 6/1959. / Lea, Pearson and Richards Architects (Box 10)
- Glenn Terrell Friendship Mall - Project Manual. 5/1993. / Architect: ALSC Architects, P.S.; Landscape Consultant: Thorson PartnershipElectrical Engineer: Doyle Engineering (Box 10)
- General Services Complex - Schematic Design Brochure. 1967. / Architect: Victor Louis Wulff, Architect. AIA and Associates; Consultants: T. R. Hance - Structural EngineersRice and Luhn - Mechanical Engineers; Wanless - Cook - Electrical Engineers (Box 10)
- General Services Complex Phase II - Program Statement. 10/1975. / Victor Louis Wulff Architect, A.LA. Associates; Atwood - Hinzman, Structural (Box 10)
- Graduate Student Residence Hall - Specifications. Drawings and Cost Estimate. 7/1969. / Walker/McGough/Foltz, Architects; Lyerla/Peden, Engineers (Box 10)
- Hazardous Waste Facilities - Schematic Design Brochure. 6/1996. / Bovay Northwest (Box 10)
- Hazardous Materials Survey - Mechanical Engineering Laboratory. 8/1994. / AGRA Earth and Environmental (Box 10)
- Hazardous Waste Facilities - Predesign Study. 6/1994. / Bovay Northwest (Box 10)
- Hazardous Material Survey - Fulmer Hall/Fulmer Annex Renovation. 7/1994. / RZA AGRA, Inc. Engineering Environmental Services (Box 10)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Report Summary Volume I The Pence Associates, Inc. / Campanella Murakami Brummitt Inc. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Guide - Memorandum, Mobility Related Improvements. 8/1988. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Persons Transition Plan for Facilities Access, Draft Number Four - University of Washington Main Campus, Pack Forest, Friday Harbor Laboratories, Richland Graduate Center. 9/1978. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Part A. Schematic Design and Design Improvement. 11/1980. / The Pence Associates, Inc.; Campanella Murakami Brummitt, Inc. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Schematic Design. Part B The Pence Associates, Inc. 11/1980. / Campanella Murakami Brummitt. Inc. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Schematic Design and Development. Supplement - Part A. 11/1980. / The Pence Associates, Inc.; Campanella Murakami Brummitt Inc. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility - Building/Site Survey (Stapled). 8/1/1998. / Campanella Murakami Brummitt Inc.; The Pence Associates, Inc. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Outline Specifications, Phase 1/Part B - 2 (Physical Plant). 6/1981. (Box 11)
- Survey of Physical Barriers Which Affect the Handicapped. 12/1977. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Construction Specifications. Phase 1. Part C - Building Retrofit / The Pence Associates, Inc.; Chisom Murakami Brummitt Inc. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Construction Documents. Phase 1, Part - Elevator Controls. 3/1981. / The Pence Associates, Inc.; Chisom Murakami Brummitt Inc. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Specs. Phase 1, Part C-1 - Building Retrofit - Nez Perce Village Unit F-Apt. 17. 9/1982. / The Pence Associates, Inc.; Chisom Murakami Brummitt Inc. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Phase I, Parts B and C Design Development. 3/1981. / The Pence Associates, Inc.; Chisom Murakami Brummitt Inc. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Construction Specifications. Phase I, part B - I Site Improvements. 10/1981. / The Pence Associates. Inc.; Chisom Murakami Brummitt Inc. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Structural Calculations. / Atwood Hinzman Consulting Engineers (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Report Summary Volume 1. / The Pence Associates, Inc.; Chisom Murakami Brummitt Inc. (Box 11)
- Remodeling for the Handicapped - Specifications. 11/1974. / Douglas C. Durkoop (Box 11)
- Remodeling for the Handicapped - Kamiak Apartments. 10/1979. (Box 11)
- Handicapped Accessibility Improvements - Schematic Design Part C. / The Pence Associates, Inc.; Campanella Murakami Brummitt Inc. (Box 11)
- WSU Map - Campus and Vicinity Wheelchair Routes and Building Access. 1978. / The Pence Associates. Inc.; Campanella Murakami Brummitt Inc. (Box 11)
- Heald Hall Fifth Floor Addition - Schematic Design Brochure. 1966. / Decker, Kolb and Stansfield Architects (Box 11)
- Heald Hall Renewal - Predesign Study. 9/1992. / The Miller Hull Partnership (Box 11)
- Hollingbery Annex - Handball/Racquet Phases I and II. Building Program. 3/1979. (Box 11)
- Hollingbery Field House Annex - Handball/Racquet - Design Development. 6/1979. / Architects: Adkison, Leigh. Sims, Cuppage; Structural Engineers: Atwood/HinzmanMechanical and Electrical: Riley Engineering (Box 11)
- Holland Library Renewal - Project Scope Development. 1/1994. / ALSC Architects (Box 11)
- Holland Library Addition - Shelving and Compact Storage Systems. Project Manual. 6/1993. / ALSC Architects. P.S. (Box 11)
- Holland Library - Specifications for Fire Pump Installation - Bid Set Drawings and Specifications/ Fire Protection and Suppression Design Alternatives. 12/1993. / Creighton Brook Engineers (Box 11)
- Holland Library Addition - Project Manual - General Construction. Volume 1 of 2. 8/1991. / ALSC Architects (Box 11)
- Holland Library Addition - Project Manual - Mechanical and Electrical. Volume 2 of 2. 8/1991. / ALSC Architects (Box 11)
- Holland Library Addition Specifications. 5/1990. / ALSC Architects, P.S. (Box 11)
- Holland Library Addition - Design Development Appendix ALSC Architects. 2/1990. / Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership (Box 11)
- Holland Library Addition - Design Development. 1/1990. / Architects. ALSC Architects, Zimmer Gunsul Frasca; Structural Engineer. Structural Design NorthwestMechanical Engineer: Riley Engineering; Electrical Engineer: Doyle Engineering; Civil Engineer: (Box 12)
- Holland Library Addition - Design Development Specification. 1/1990. / ALSC Architects, P.S.; Zimmer Gunsul Grasca Partnership (Box 12)
- Holland Library Addition - Preliminary Design. 11/1989. / Architects: ALSC Architects. Zimmer Gunsul Frasca; Structural Engineer: Structural Design NorthwestMechanical Engineer: Riley Engineering; Electrical Engineer: Doyle Engineering; Civil Engineer: (Box 12)
- Holland Library Addition and Renewal. Site Design and Building Massing Studies. 5/1989. / ALSC Architects, Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership; Structural: Suden Golden and GuestMechanical: Riley Engineering; Electrical: Wanless Cook; Civil: Wyatt Jaykim; Libr (Box 12)
- Holland Library Addition - Preliminary Site Studies and Cost Estimates. 3/1989. / Architects: ALSC Architects; Design Architects: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership (Box 12)
- Holland Library Addition - Schematic Design Architects: ALSC Architects. 7/1989. / Design Architects: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership (Box 12)
- Holland Library Addition and Renewal - Architect Selection Interview. 9/1988. / Architects: ALSC Architects; Design Architects: Zimmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership (Box 12)
- Holland Library Renovation - Partial Schematic Design for Full Renovation and Design Development for Phase One. 9/1980. / Joyce/Nordfors and Associates, P.S. (Box 12)
- Holland Renovation - Program. 3/1980. (Box 12)
- Holland Library for State College of Washington. 1947. / Schematic Design Brochure (Box 12)
- HVAC Design Analysis (Incinerator). 10/1997. / Prepared By Bovay Northwest, Inc. (Box 12)
- Incinerator Building - Specifications - Volume 1. 8/1998. (Box 12)
- Incinerator Building - Specifications - Volume 2. 8/1998. (Box 12)
- Incinerator Project - Civil Design Analysis. 10/1997. / Prepared By Bovay Northwest, Inc. (Box 12)
- Incinerator Study - Incinerator Report. 8/1991. / Wieland, Lindgren and Associates, Inc. (Box 12)
- Incinerator Study - Reasonable Available Control Technology. 11/1994. / Bovay Northwest; EnviromechDames and Moore (Box 12)
- Incinerator - Site Selection Study for Pathological Waste incinerator. 2/1995. / Bovay Northwest (Box 12)
- Incinerator Opinion of Probable Costs for Pathological and Solid Waste Incinerators. 3/1995. / Bovay Northwest (Box 12)
- Incinerator - Environmental Impact Statement for Replacement Medical Waste. Incinerator, Volume 1 of II. (Needs to Be Pulled and Tossed. A Complete Set Volume I and II are in Box # 29.). 10/1996. / WSU (Box 12)
- Incinerator - Geotechnical Report on Storage Building Gifford Consultants, Inc. 11/1992. (Box 12)
- Incinerator - Environmental Health and Safety Plan Review Record. Notice of Construction. 1/1998. / Envirotech Drawings (Box 12)
- Incinerator - Notice of Construction Application Declaring Intent to Construct, Install, or Establish A New Air Contaminant Source or Replacement or Substantial Alteration of Emission Control Technology on an Existing Stationary Source. Attachment: Proces (Box 12)
- Incinerator. / Envirotech Drawings (Box 12)
- Incinerator - New incinerator Building - Utility Study. 2/1997. / Bovay Northwest A Dames and Moore Subsidiary (Box 12)
- Incinerator - Schematic Design Brochure. 3/1997. / Bovay Northwest, Inc.; EnviroMech (Box 12)
- Incinerator - Design Development Submittal. 7/1997. / Bovay Northwest (Box 12)
- Incinerator - Conceptual Design Analysis for Medical Waste Incinerator. 1/1997. / Bovay Northwest; EnviroMech (Box 12)
- Incinerator Project - Design Development: Outline Specifications Submittal. 7/1997. / Bovay Northwest A Dames and Moore Subsidiary (Box 12)
- Incinerator - Bidders Equipment List, Technical Data and Guarantees. 1/1998. / Bovay Northwest (Box 12)
- Incinerator Upgrades - Trade Specifications. 9/1995. / Bovay Northwest (Box 13)
- Intercollegiate Center For Nursing Education - Project Manual (Yakima). 1/1995. / Architect: Integrus Architecture, P.S.; Structural Engineer: Structural Design Northwest. Inc.Mechanical and Electrical Engineers: MW Consulting Engineers (Box 13)
- Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education - Project Manual (Yakima). 11/1994. / Architect: Integrus Architecture. P.S.; Structural Engineer: Structural Design Northwest, Inc.Mechanical and Electrical Engineers: MW Consulting Engineers (Box 13)
- Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education (Spokane) - Design Development / Walker McGough Foltz Lyerla. 10/1976. (Box 13)
- Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education - Joint EWSC - WSU Building Program. 3/1976. (Box 13)
- Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education (Yakima) - Design Development. 8/1994. / Architect: Integrus Architecture, P.S.; Structural Engineer: Structural Design Northwest, Inc.Mechanical and Electrical Engineers: MW Consulting Engineers (Box 13)
- Johnson Hall Specifications for Remodel Rooms 101, 122, 184, 190, 387, 396 and 39. By the Board of Regents Of WSU. 6/1994. (Box 13)
- Johnson Hall Addition - Schematic Design Brochure. 10/1978. / Architect: Gayne L Jones and Associates; Structural: Charles E. KitchinMechanical: Valentine. Fisher, and Tomlinson; Electrical: Beverly A. Travis (Box 13)
- Kimbrough Hall - Specifications for General Contract - Books 1,2, and 3. 2/1964. / Ralph E. Decker, AIA Architects; Administrative Architect: Gary L. Shavey. AIAUniversity Architect: Philip E. Keene, AIA (Box 13)
- Kimbrough Hall Addition - Predesign Study - Books 1,2, and 3. 6/1992. / Predesign Consultants: Thompson Vaivoda and Associates, Architects AIA; In Association With Heylman Martin and Associates, Architects, AIA (Box 13)
- Kimbrough Hall - Asbestos Abatement Submittals by Tektoniks Corp. 6/1997. / Tektonics Corporation (Box 14)
- Kimbrough Music Building - Pictures and Design Plans. 3/1966. / Ralph E. Decker AIA Architects (Box 14)
- Kimbrough Hall - Preliminary Presentation. 1/1963. / Ralph E. Decker AIA Architects (Box 14)
- Kimbrough Music Building - A Program for an Addition to. 5/1970. (Box 14)
- Kimbrough Hall Addition and Renewal - Bid Set Volume One. 3/1998. / Architect: Thompson Vaivoda and Assoc. Archs; Structural: kpff Consulting EngineersCivil: Rosewater Engineering; Mechanical and Electrical Glumac; Landscape: Murase and Associates; Acoustica (Box 14)
- Kimbrough Hall Addition and Renewal - Bid Set Volume Two. 3/1998. / Architect: Thompson Vaivoda and Assoc. Arch's; Structural: kpff Consulting EngineersCivil: Rosewater Engineering; Mechanical and Electrical: Glumac; Landscape: Murase and Associates; Acoustic (Box 14)
- Kimbrough Hall Addition and Renewal - Addendum Two. 4/1998. / Prepared by Thompson Vaivoda and Associates, Architects AIA. (Box 14)
- Kimbrough Hall Addition and Renewal - Design Development Set Project Manual. 5/1996. / Thompson Vaivoda and Associates Architects, Inc. (Box 14)
- Kimbrough Hall Renovation - Hazardous Materials Abatement Project. (Box 14)
- Abatement Specifications and Contract Documents. 5/1997. / Prepared By: Edward S. DeLorme While Employed By: SCM Consultants, Inc. (Box 14)
- Kimbrough Hall - Asbestos Abatement Project - Final Report. 12/1997. / Prepared by Richard A. Johnson, CIH SCM Consultants, Inc. (Box 14)
- Kimbrough Hall - Addition and Renewal - Schematic Design. 1/1996. / Architect: Thompson Vaivoda and Associates Architects AIA; Associated Architect: Heylman Martin and AssociatesStructural: kpff Consulting Engineers; Mechanical and Electrical: Glumac Internatio (Box 14)
- Launch Boathouse and Dock - Building Program 84 - 85. / McKinley Nance Director of Facilities Planning (Box 14)
- Laboratory Animal Resources Facility - Building Program. 8/1970. / Mr. Owen Bradvold - Office of Facilities Planning Liaison and Advisory Architect (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Additions - Second Floor. 10/1969. / Architects: Culler Gale Martell Ericson; Engineer: Kenneth P. Norrie (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall - South Addition. 4/1970. / Architects: Culler Gale Martell Ericson; Engineer: Kenneth P. Norrie (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall - Completion of South and Anatomy Refrigeration Room. 11/1971. / Architects: Culler Gale Martell Ericson; Engineer: Kenneth P. Norrie (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Remodeling - Building Program 1 of 2. 4/1978. (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Remodeling - Building Program 2 of 2. 4/1978. (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Remodeling - Schematic Design Brochure. 10/1978. / Culler Gale Martell and Ericson. Architects (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Remodeling - General Specifications. 9/1979. / Culler Gale Martell Ericson P.S. (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Phase 11 - Building Program. 6/1982. (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Remodeling Phase 11 - Schematic Design Brochure. 2/1983. / Culler Gale Marteil and Ericson, Architects (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Remodeling/Renovation Program. 11/1985. (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Remodeling/Renewal Program Phase II. 4/1986. (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Renewal - Schematic Phase. 3/1987. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates; Peter A. SudenTres West Engineers, Inc. (Box 14)
- McCoy Hall Renewal - Project Manual. 12/1987. / De Neff Deeble Barton Associates (Box 14)
- Martin Stadium and Academic Center North Stands Replacement - Schematic Design Brochure/Some Pictures. / Naramore Bain Brady and Johanson Architects Engineers Planners (Box 14)
- Martin Stadium - Fire Lane Route Study. 7/1997. / PPL Coffman Project# 95027-03 (Box 14)
- Martin Stadium - Schematic Design Brochure, Academic Athletic Complex (Lengthwise along box). 3/1972. / Naramore Bain Brady and Johanson Architects Engineers Planners (Box 14)
- Murrow Hall Renovation/Addition - Predesign Study. 6/1998. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 15)
- Morrill Hall Remodeling - Design Development. 9/1979. / Ralph D. Anderson and Partners; Booth and Koch Architects (Box 15)
- Morrill Hall Remodeling - Construction Details, As Built. 12/1981. / Ralph D. Anderson and Partners/Booth and Koch Architects and Environmental Planners (Box 15)
- Murrow Remodeling - Schematic Design Brochure. 1971. / Architects and Planners: De Neff Deeble Barton Associates; Mechanical: Rice and LuhnElectrical: Wanless - Cook (Box 15)
- Murrow - Schematic Design Brochure. 7/1969. / Architects and Planners: De Neff Deeble Barton Associates; Mechanical: Rice and LuhnElectrical: Wanless - Cook; Structural: Peter Suden (Box 15)
- Murrow - Department of Communications Student Publications Radio - Television Services - Building Program Statement. (Box 15)
- Memorial Hospital Study - Schematic Design Brochure. 1/1976. / Architects and Planners: De Neff Deeble Barton Associates; Mechanical: Rice and LuhnElectrical: Wanless - Cook; Structural: Peter Suden (Box 15)
- Meats Laboratory - Schematic Design Brochure. 9/1964. / Barnard and Holloway Architects (Box 15)
- Meats Laboratory - Schematic Design Brochure Phase II. / Barnard and Holloway Architects (Box 15)
- Married Student Apartments - Kamiak 100 Unit. 1964. / McClure and Adkison Architects AIA (Box 15)
- Neill Hall Renewal - Specifications. 2/1988. / Anderson Koch and Duane (Box 15)
- Neill Hall Renewal - Final Cost Estimate. 3/1989. / Duarte Bryant Architecture (Box 15)
- Neill Hall Renewal - Schematic Phase. 1988. / Anderson Koch and Duarte; United Pacific EngineersLee Engineering; Travis Fitzmaurice and Associates, Inc. (Box 15)
- Neill Hall Renewal - Building Program. 5/1987. (Box 15)
- North-South Ski Lodge - Design Development Phase I. 2/1976. / Architects: Adkison Leigh Sims Cuppage; Structural: L.C. CampbellMechanical and Electrical: Riley Engineering (Box 15)
- Nuclear Reactor Building. Addition to. 3/1967. / Miller and Fiedler - Architects AIA (Box 15)
- Orton Hall - Schematic Design Brochure. 6/1962. / Philip E. Keene - University Architect; Lea, Pearson and Richards - Architects (Box 15)
- Rogers Hall - Mens Residence Tower. 5/1961. / Philip E. Keene - University Architect; Lea, Pearson, and Richards - Architects (Box 15)
- Rogers/Orton Site Plan for Residence Halls. 6/1962. / Resume of Richard Haag Associates; Landscape Architects - Planning Consultants (Box 15)
- Owen Science Library - Foundation Investigation. 6/1974. / For Harris, Reed and Litzenberger Architects, AIA; By: Shannon and Wilson, Inc. - Geotechnical Consultants (Box 15)